https://www.beatricearthur.com/privacy-policy/

Who we are
Our website address is: https://www.beatricearthur.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Additional information
How we protect your data
What data breach procedures we have in place
What third parties we receive data from
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Like Bea!
Like Bea!
Buy me a coffeeAli Forney Center
Art Attack Foundation At artattackfoundation.org, fans of Ms. Arthur's can find genuine and authentic items autographed and donated by Bea and her friends that are being sold on ebay for this worthy charity. It is a good cause, raising money for student scholarships in the performing arts.
Subscribe via Email
Enter your email address to subscribe to this blog and receive notifications of new posts by email.
Email Address
Subscribe
Search for:
RSS Feed
Recent Posts
10 years since Bea’s passing
The Amazing World of the Golden Girls
The Bea Arthur Residence Building Dedication
Recent CommentsVincentReawl on Happy Birthday to Bea ArthurEllisCat on Happy Birthday to Bea ArthurTate Christina on News posts for year 2001James on The Golden Girls gracefully arrives on iTunesJames on The Golden Girls gracefully arrives on iTunesArchives Archives
Select Month
May 2019  (1)
January 2018  (1)
December 2017  (1)
January 2017  (2)
October 2016  (1)
May 2016  (1)
April 2016  (1)
March 2016  (1)
September 2015  (1)
July 2015  (1)
May 2015  (2)
April 2015  (1)
December 2014  (1)
November 2014  (1)
May 2014  (1)
April 2014  (1)
March 2014  (1)
February 2014  (2)
November 2013  (1)
May 2013  (1)
February 2013  (1)
November 2012  (1)
September 2012  (1)
May 2012  (1)
January 2012  (1)
January 2011  (1)
December 2010  (2)
November 2010  (1)
June 2010  (1)
May 2010  (1)
April 2010  (1)
January 2010  (1)
October 2009  (1)
September 2009  (2)
August 2009  (1)
June 2009  (1)
May 2009  (2)
April 2009  (3)
February 2009  (1)
December 2008  (2)
September 2008  (1)
August 2008  (1)
July 2008  (1)
June 2008  (1)
May 2008  (2)
April 2008  (1)
November 2007  (1)
August 2007  (1)
June 2007  (2)
May 2007  (1)
March 2007  (5)
February 2007  (2)
January 2007  (1)
December 2006  (1)
November 2006  (3)
October 2006  (1)
September 2006  (3)
August 2006  (4)
July 2006  (1)
June 2006  (1)
May 2006  (3)
April 2006  (1)
March 2006  (3)
February 2006  (2)
January 2006  (2)
December 2005  (4)
November 2005  (4)
October 2005  (3)
September 2005  (4)
August 2005  (2)
July 2005  (4)
June 2005  (2)
May 2005  (4)
April 2005  (3)
March 2005  (5)
February 2005  (3)
January 2005  (5)
January 2004  (1)
January 2003  (1)
January 2002  (1)
January 2001  (1)
January 2000  (1)
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Okay!Privacy policy
